<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Alice Y Taylor</title><link>https://aliceyt24.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Alice Y Taylor</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aliceyt24.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://aliceyt24.github.io/biography/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 18:56:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aliceyt24.github.io/biography/</guid><description>I am a Global Justice postdoctoral scholar at University of Denver&amp;rsquo;s Korbel School of International Affairs. I completed my Ph.D. at the University of California, Berkeley School of Education in 2023, with a designated emphasis in Gender &amp;amp; Women&amp;rsquo;s Studies. An interdisciplinary social scientist and ethnographer, I study education and social movements including youth political and civic engagement; sociocultural approaches to language, literacies, and learning across in-person and digital spaces; and interconnections between local and global structures of oppression and resistance.</description></item><item><title>Select Research Reports and Educational Materials</title><link>https://aliceyt24.github.io/select-research-reports/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 18:56:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aliceyt24.github.io/select-research-reports/</guid><description>Gupta, T. P., Taylor, A. Y., Lauro, G., Shengelia, L., Sturua, L. (2018). Exploring practices of early/child marriage and FGM/C in Georgia: Results from qualitative research. Tblisi, Georgia and Washington DC: National Center for Disease Control and Public Health, Promundo US, United Nations Population Fund, United Nations Children’s Fund.
Vaitla, B., Taylor, A. Y., Van Horn, J., Cislaghi, B. (2017). Social norms and girls’ well-being: Linking theory and practice. Washington, D.</description></item></channel></rss>